HERON CAKIQI

Full Stack Engineer

INFO

PHONE

+38344755183

EMAIL

cakiqiheron@gmail.com

LINKS

Portfolio

<u>Github</u>

CodePen

SKILLS

JavaScript

ReactJS

Redux

Node.js

Express.js

LANGUAGES

Albanian

English

German

PROFILE

A full-stack JavaScript developer since 2016 with a passion for the functionality of Web Applications. Through the past 3 years I have built lots of real world side projects and also participated in different university projects always using the latest web development technologies such as ReactJs, React Native, Redux, Node.js, Express.js, and MongoDB. Also currently I'm active in the role of the ReactJs Developer.

EDUCATION

University for Business and Technology (UBT)

Information Systems

Oct 2013 — Present

All courses completed but not graduated.

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

ReactJs/React Native Developer, Albanian Telecommunication & Information Services

Jan 2020 — Present

- · Building highly functional and modern UI-s
- · Using the latest technologies and best practice patterns

Manager, SKY TRAVEL L.L.C

Jan 2017 — Jan 2020

General Manager in a travel agency business.

Computer Network Architect, Expert NSHT

Jun 2015 — Dec 2016

Built different data communication local area networks (LANs) on as need basis in different offices and work places.

Agent, SCARDIAN J.S.C.

Jun 2017 — Oct 2019

Insurance sales agent.